JOSE ARMAS

Boca Raton, Florida 954-461-3564

JoseArmasLeon@Gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jlarmas92/

Proactive professional with 6+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of customer needs assessments, procedure standardization and process simplification. Bilingual individual aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill a management role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

TOUCHSUITE, BOCA RATON, FL

2016 - PRESENT

OPERATIONS SUPERVISOR

2019 - PRESENT

- Support the delivery of proactive and responsive support to our customers that is timely, professional, and accurate
- Ensure that the work of team members is measured against expectations through quality control
- Planning and controlling change across Departments which include Merchant Support/Maintenance of the book of business, Sales Agent Support, New Applications through Deployment, Quality Control and PCI/general compliance
- Researching new technologies and alternative methods of efficiency
- Serve as an escalation point for the Operations department in order to resolve high priority issues in a promptly manner
- Administer, maintain & onboard new employees on TouchSuite UniversityTM
- Integral in implementing Salesforce as TouchSuite's new CRM.

SALES & PARTNER SUPPORT MANAGER

2018 - 2019

- Understand, breakdown, analyze and restructure company processes.
- Create, maintain & support TouchSuite UniversityTM. Work cross departmentally to collect and publish accurate knowledge base for our employees and partners.
- Responsible for Agent Boarding Department, collecting, proofing and archiving relevant documentation of agents.
- Communicate and provide proper credentials for secure sites on TouchSuite & Partner platforms.
- Manage the Sales & Partner Support Department by working cross functionally between Sales & Operations.
- Seek out solutions from challenges that arise during the sales process.
- Triage, review & escalate issues submitted, as well as, offer TouchSuite Simple support to employees and partners through proprietary systems.

PROJECT MANAGER 2016 – 2018

- Analyze & restructure processes for every department to have a direct flow that any employee can follow. Departments include: Agent Boarding, POS Setup, Simple Signup, Terminal Guide, Tech Support, USA Boarding, Canada Boarding.
- Understand the need for Sales Support, create an issue tracker and document inquiries in order to better deliver a solution.
- Oversee appointment setters by tracking their progress and send weekly reports to the Vice-President of Sales regarding the conversion rate using Google Forms while transitioning into Salesforce.
- Support the developers in testing the new features of our on-boarding platform including all processors. First line of response for Intercom, assigning issues that arise to the correct department.

- Compile courses for TouchSuite UniversityTM. Revise marketing materials that are translated to Spanish to ensure the language used is correct prior to publishing.
- Work closely with management team to understand their needs and develop innovative strategies around finding top talent. Identify recruiting sources, assess new talent, and develop methods to attract diverse talent.
- Develop, manage and execute a consistent recruitment plan, while sourcing a high-volume flow of qualified candidates through active and passive sourcing methods.
- Assist with any HR related tasks such as preparing offer letters, updating HR documents, and on-boarding new hires.

HAPPY FEET SOCCER SOUTH FLORIDA, BOCA RATON, FL 2013 – PRESENT PT ASSISTANT DIRECTOR OF COACHING

- Educate the youth (2 years old to 12 years old) in the importance of staying active and how it can positively impact your life.
- Strategic Consulting, locating the best site where more customers can be reached as well as ensuring the company has the most cost-efficient deal.

Customer Service is something we pride ourselves in, constant communication is 75% of our job, we need to make sure the parents are aware of everything that is going on as well as an update on their child's progress.

EDUCATION

FLORIDA ATLANTIC UNIVERSITY, BOCA RATON, FL BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN ECONOMICS

GRADUATED 2017

SALEM INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY, SALEM, WV ASSOCIATES OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION AND MANAGEMENT, GRADUATED 2012

LAUNCHCODE LC 101, COMPUTER SCIENCE

2019 - PRESENT

Technologies Learned: Python, C#, SQL, Web Development

LEADERSHIP

- National Society of Collegiate Scholars (NSCS)
- Alpha Psi Lambda (ΑΨΛ)
- Fraternity & Sorority Life Council
- Students Advocating Volunteer Involvement
- Leadershape Institute

- NCAA Division II Soccer Athlete
- Student Athlete Advisory Committee
- Information Technology Student Organization
- Diverbo Volunteer Instructor